<?xml version="1.0"?>
<FAQ><description>&lt;div class="main-title" style="text-transform: uppercase; font-size: 26px; color: rgb(44, 44, 44); margin-top: 18px; margin-bottom: 15px;"&gt;&lt;div class="main-title" style="margin-top: 18px; margin-bottom: 15px; text-align: justify;"&gt;PRIVACY POLICY.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;&lt;div class="flip" style="color: rgb(247, 148, 30); font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;Data &amp; Usage&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;This Privacy Policy explains how Retailgenius collects personal and non-personal information, classified as compulsory or voluntary. Disclosing and protecting such information through the Website, Retailgenius PROHIBITS the trade or sale of Your personal Information in any form or manner, except as specified herein or if express consent is sought from You.&nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Personal Information provided by You is used only for the following:&lt;ol&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Facilitating Your use of the Website&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Responding to Your inquiries or fulfill Your requests for information&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Providing You with information about Retailgenius&#x2019;s products/services and to send You information on promotions and offers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sending You essential information regarding the Website, changes to Retailgenius terms, conditions, and policies and/or other administrative information&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Providing You surveys and marketing communications that may be of interest to You&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Giving You a personalized experience on the Website and other websites by presenting advertising, products and offers tailored to Your needs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Providing help to Your problems with the Website or any technical problems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;If You purchase any product or benefit of a service from the Retailgenius, to complete and fulfill Your purchase, e.g. to have Your payments processed, we will communicate with You regarding Your purchase and provide You with related customer service&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;For proper administration of the Retailgenius Website&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Conducting internal reviews and data analysis for the Website (e.g., determining the volume of visitors to specific pages within the Website)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improving services, content and advertising on Retailgenius.com&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Protecting the integrity of the Website &amp; responding to any legal processes and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as legalized by law&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;&lt;div class="flip" style="color: rgb(247, 148, 30); font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;Sharing Personal Information&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;It is essential that You submit Your Information at the time of making an online purchase on the Website. Retailgenius utilizes online payment gateways that are operated by a third party. The information You provide to Retailgenius is shared with the relevant third party payment gateway operator to ensure a smooth experience when using and purchasing on the Website. The operator may access Your Retailgenius purchase history that You make.&lt;br&gt;Sensitive information such as Your credit card details are transferred through secure and trusted/approved payment gateways which are digitally encrypted. Providing the best available and possible care up-to-date with such technology to handle Your sensitive information. You are to be advised that internet technology is not 100% safe and you as a user should be cautious.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;&lt;div class="flip" style="color: rgb(247, 148, 30); font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;Third Party Websites&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;The Website will on occasion provide third-party linked advertisements on this Website. Retailgenius will NOT provide any Personal Information to these-third-party websites or advertisers.&lt;br&gt;Retailgenius will contain links to other websites on the website which are controlled and operated by third parties. These sites are not controlled by, or associated with Retailgenius unless it has been clearly specified on the Retailgenius Website. Retailgenius does not take responsibility for any communication You receive from these linked sites. These-third-party websites may also use technology to follow and send advertisements on the website to Your browser. In such case, the-third-party website/advertisers will automatically receive Your IP address, use cookies, JavaScript and other technologies to measure the progress and effectiveness of their advertisements.&lt;br&gt;Retailgenius does not control or assure the accuracy, quality of any type content represented on these-third-party websites Additionally Retailgenius will not represent the privacy practices or policies conducted by these third party sites.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;&lt;div class="flip" style="color: rgb(247, 148, 30); font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;Security&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;Retailgenius pursues the best security for the Integrity of Your Personal Information and to help protect Your Personal Information against unauthorized access/alteration, exposure or mishandling. Retailgenius implements the latest practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where Retailgenius stores Your personal data.&nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Retailgenius does not take responsibility for any breach of security or actions of any third parties that receive Your Personal Information as this is beyond our control.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;&lt;div class="flip" style="color: rgb(247, 148, 30); font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;Disclosure&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;Retailgenius utilize information only in accordance with the Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received clear authorization.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;&lt;div class="flip" style="color: rgb(247, 148, 30); font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;User Discretion&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;You as the user can always decide to not provide information. Such cases where the information required is classified as compulsory, You will not be able to benefit that part of the Service, feature or content available on the Website. When You add/update Personal Information on a regular basis, Retailgenius will obtain a prior copy of versions for its records. If You do not require Retailgenius to use Personal Information, please report to&nbsp;&lt;a href="mailto:[info@retailgenius.com]" style="color: rgb(51, 122, 183);"&gt;info@retailgenius.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;&lt;div class="flip" style="color: rgb(247, 148, 30); font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;General Provisions&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;By accessing the Website, You have agreed to the terms set out in this Policy. This Policy should be at all times be read along with the Terms of the Website.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;&lt;div class="flip" style="color: rgb(247, 148, 30); font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;Complaint Representative&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; text-align: justify; text-transform: none;"&gt;For complaints or concerns including those relating to breach of Retailgenius Terms, policies for Sale and other polices or questions are published as under:&nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 700;"&gt;Complaint Representative Name:&lt;/span&gt;&nbsp;Privacy Team&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 700;"&gt;Email Address:&lt;/span&gt;&nbsp;&lt;a href="mailto:[info@retailgenius.com]" style="color: rgb(51, 122, 183);"&gt;info@retailgenius.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 700;"&gt;Availability:&lt;/span&gt;&nbsp;Monday to Friday, 09:00 AM to 6:00 PM&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description></FAQ>
